{
	"questionlist" :[{
		"question" : "Definition: A program that performs a particular task, such as texting and calling.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Application"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Feature"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Component"}],
		"correct" : 1
	},
	{
		"question" : "Definition: Parts of a device that makes the device function.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Device"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Component"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Application"}],
		"correct" : 2
	},
	{
		"question" : "Definition: A state of being.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Component"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Feature"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Condition"}],
		"correct" : 3
	},
	{
		"question" : " Definition: A piece of equipment or a mechanism designed to serve a special purpose or perform a special function.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Device"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Function"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Feature"}],
		"correct" : 1
	},
	{
		"question" : "Definition: The structure, form, or appearance.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Device"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Function"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Feature"}],
		"correct" : 2
	},
	{
		"question" : " Definition: The special purpose or activity for which a thing exists or is used.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Condition"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Feature"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Function"}],
		"correct" : 3
	},
	{
		"question" : " Definition: Reception of knowledge or intelligence.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Information"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Technology"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Telecommunication"}],
		"correct" : 1
	},
	{
		"question" : "Definition: Act of placing or arranging.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Condition"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Position"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Feature"}],
		"correct" : 2
	},
	{
		"question" : " Definition: Practical application of knowledge, particularly in certain area.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Information"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Technology"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Telecommunication"}],
		"correct" : 2
	},
	{
		"question" : " Definition: Communication at a distance.",
		"answerlist" : [{"key" : 1, "answer":"Information"},{"key" : 2, "answer":"Telecommunication"},{"key" : 3, "answer":"Technology"}],
		"correct" : 2
	}]
}